我不知道这是要去哪里
I don't know where I'm going.
开你的车就行了
Just keep driving.
我这样怎么把得住方向盘
How am I supposed to hold the wheel like this?
我根本就无法开车
I can barely steer.
你开得还行
You're doing fine.
博伊特  我们有事好商量
Voight, there's got to be a deal we can make.
这里停车
Pull over up here.
出来  我们走
Come on, let's go.
快走
Let's go.
这是四千块  你放了我的话...
This is 4 grand, if you just let me--
-放我走吧  -闭嘴  给我过来
- Just let me go. - Shut up. Come here.
有三个孩子吸毒过量致死了
I got three dead kids who OD'd,
我再问你一次
so I'm asking one more time.
有问题的毒品是谁卖的
Who's putting out the bad dope?
我说过了
I told you!
我要名字  名字
The name. A name!
雷夫  那个人叫雷夫
Rev. His name is Rev.
他在南翡翠大道的一栋公寓里卖毒品
He deals out of an apartment on South Emerald.
看着我
Look at me.
看到没有
See that?
你要是敢越过这条线
You ever cross that line,
下次你就得去河底走一遭了
the next trip you take will be to the bottom of the river.
不准再踏入芝加哥
Stay out of my city.
给你搭车
Bus fare.
今天谁要开心地去上学呀
Who's excited for school today?
-不是我哦  -叮咚
- Not me. - Knock, knock.
请问哪位呀
Who's there?
好  这是利亚姆拍照的钱
Okay, photo day for Liam.
-不公平  -这是艾米的班费
- Hey, that's not fair. - Classroom fund for Emmy.
-叮咚  -哪位呀
- Knock, knock. - Who is there?
-哪张是给艾米的来着  -艾米吗
- Which one's Emmy? - Emmy?
喂  爸爸
Hello, dad!
-艾米有事吗  -是我啊
- Emmy? - It's me!
知道了  放心
Got it. Got it.
要一直提醒我哦  宝贝
Keep reminding me, sweetie.
-叮咚  -谁呀
- Knock, knock. - Who's there?
你一定很高兴我没有说香蕉吧
Bet you're glad I didn't say banana.
差不多吧  宝贝
Close enough, baby.
你们好呀  威尔海特这一大家子
What's up, Willhites?
今晚吃黄金意面哦
Million-dollar spaghetti tonight.
-大家拜拜  -你怎么一身汗
- See you guys. - Oh, you're all sweaty.
好像刚从健身房出来
Looks like you just went to the gym.
我才不会说我确实刚从健身房过来
I won't tell you I just came from the gym.
恶心不恶心  走开
You're gross. Get away from me.
我早就说过  你要是办年卡的话
I told you--I can get you a 20% cop discount
我可以帮你打八折的警官折扣
on a year membership.
-早啊  美女  -真好笑
- Morning, sunshine. - Funny.
不是钱的问题  是时间问题
It's not the money. It's the time.
我去剪个头发都得申请休假
I got to take furlough just to get my hair cut.
显然那玩意儿会害死你的
That stuff will kill ya now, apparently.
网上看到过的一篇文章
Saw an article online.
我要关心的事多着呢
Well, that is last on the very long list
可没功夫去想这个
of things that I'm concerned about.
谢谢
Please.
凯特琳问起过你
Caitlin was asking about you.
是吗  帮我向她问好
Oh, yeah. Tell her I say hi.
也就是说你不感兴趣吗
So no interest on your part?
她人超好  可我没那个福分
She's super sweet, but my loss.
你们看到博伊特了吗
Hey, you guys seen Voight around?
没看到  怎么了
No. Why?
没事
Nothing.
我以后可再也不帮你介绍对象了
You--I am never setting you up again.
什么  为什么
What? Why not?
因为你这个人审美有问题
Because you don't know a good thing when you see it.
知道那个毒贩子的名字了
Got a name on that dealer.
很好  去抓他吧
Good. Get him off the street.
你瞧好吧
Watch me.
等等
Hey, hold up.
长官
Sir.
进来  把门关上
Come on in. Close the door.
我想跟你把事情缕一缕
I'm just trying to do the math here.
几个月前  你跟人达成协议
A few months ago, you work out a deal,
不仅出狱了  还不知怎么的
get yourself out of jail, and somehow,
拿到了市局里最重要的工作
you land the biggest job in the city--
在我的辖区内负责一个情报机构
running an intelligence unit in my district.
对  是这样的
Yeah, things worked out.
我跟你说  我不得不承认
I tell ya-- I got no choice to admit
你跟上头之间的联系
that, somehow, you are connected upstairs in ways
我是不理解的
that I do not understand.
但是  警长
But, sergeant...
为什么内务部有个
why the hell is a woman named Gradishar
叫格拉迪沙尔的女人打电话问你的事
from internal affairs calling me up about you?
是叫格拉迪沙尔吗
You say Gradishar?
没听过这个人
Never heard of her.
如果你继续不按规矩办事
If you're still running game out on the street, cowboy,
干些违法的勾当
being a dirty cop,
我会亲自把你赶出警界的
I will personally throw you off a roof.
指挥官回见
Commander.
阿特沃特  伯吉斯
Atwater, Burgess.
-是  警长  -找你们有事
- Yes, sergeant. - Need you today.
遵命
You got it.
-警长  -怎么了
- Sergeant. - What?
博斯今天给我看了点路边发生的事
Pods showed me something off the side of the road today--
你跟丹·瑞安之间见面的事
Confrontation off the Dan Ryan.
-被录下来了吗  -被录下来了
- It was on camera? - It was on camera.
先过去
Go.
-但不会再出现了  -不会了
- But not any longer? - No.
那就好
I can live with that.
好  大家听着
All right, listen up.
我找到吸毒致死案件的责任人了
Got a name on those dope deaths.
是南翡翠大道那边一个叫雷夫的毒贩子
It's a dealer named Rev on South Emerald.
奥林斯基一到  我们就...
As soon as Olinsky gets here, we're gonna--
我在这呢
Over here.
你好  埃尔文
Hey, Alvin.
汉克
Hank.
我们要进行一次卧底买卖
We're gonna set up a controlled buy--
霍斯特德和琳德赛去敲门问情况
Halstead and Lindsay in the doorway.
但千万不要进门
Do not go inside.
明白
Got it.
好了  还有一件事
All right, one more thing--
我们已经共事...有两个月了吧
We've been doing this, what, two months?
从现在开始一定要谨慎
Now more than ever,
所有消息都不能外泄
we keep everything in house.
明白吗
Understand?
我不管别的部门怎么工作
I don't care how they run other departments
也不管你是什么来历
or how you came up.
但这里是情报组  是我的部门
This is intelligence-- my unit.
你们跟我实话实话  我才能罩着你们
You tell me the truth, so I can lie for you.
如果你们有谁敢在我这里越权办事
And if you ever go over my head,
那将会是你们最后一次越权
it'll be the last head you go over.
今晚大家都回去好好休息
Everybody goes home tonight.
你想知道一个绰号
You want to know how you can tell
是怎么流行开来的吗
when a nickname sticks?
十年前  十六街的小混混们
Ten years ago, the corner boys on 16th Street
开始叫我"八爪"  就是章鱼的意思
started calling me Pulpo, the octopus.
为什么呢
Why?
因为我的势力无处不在
Because I had my hands everywhere.
富勒顿的小子
A drop on Fullerton,
洪堡公园的士兵
a couple of soldiers in Humboldt Park--
都是我搞定的
I handled it.
这样"八爪"就开始声名远扬了
I started hearing the name Pulpo everywhere,
从街头毒贩的嘴里到妓女的唇边
from street dealers' mouths to whores' lips.
你知道别人背后都叫你什么吗
You want to know what they call you behind your back?
长舌男[西语]
Chismoso,
因为你的舌头总会
because your tongue is always flapping
在不该动的时候乱动
when it shouldn't be...
所以我才把你抓来
Which is why I'm here.
了结他[西语]
Acabemos con esto.
雷夫  开门
Rev! Open up!
我说你能点小声吗
Hey! You mind keeping it down?
我砸你们门了吗  没吧
Am I banging on your door? No?
回你的家去
Then go back inside.
雷夫  开门
Rev, open up!
我这是在冒险  雷夫可能不在家
I'm going out on a limb here. Rev might not be home.
快点开门  兄弟
Come on, man!
什么事
What?
雷夫在家吗
Yeah, uh, is Rev here?
不在  所以你别敲了
No, so quit pounding on the door.
兄弟  我女朋友
Hey, man, yo, my girl--
她明天要去戒毒所了
she's going into rehab tomorrow.
今晚想来点刺激的
Wants to go out with a bang tonight.
我一直都是和雷夫联系的
Rev usually hooks me up.
你去过戒毒所吗  那里根本不是人待的
You ever been to rehab, man? It sucks.
进来吧
Come in.
我们等雷夫回来了再来
We'll come back when Rev's here.
你缠了我两个小时
You've been up my ass for two hours
嚷嚷着要买点"那个"
about scoring some "H".
人家改主意了嘛
Well, I changed my mind!
女人就是善变  是吧
Mujeres, right?
那个看上去像是血迹
It looked like blood.
外加我们不认识那个男的...
That and the fact that we don't know that guy--
你不用解释
You don't have to justify it.
你们差点搞砸了  就是差点搞砸了
You got a bad hit, you got a bad hit.
我们闯进去吧
Let's go in.
不行  就因为看上去像是血迹
No. 'Cause maybe it looked like blood?
不足以执行强行突入
That's not probable cause to force an entry.
他可能在腌鸡肉的时候
He could have been marinating a chicken
不小心把烤肉酱洒在了裤子上
and spilled barbecue sauce on his pants.
三件吸毒过量致死案
We've got three O.D.s
都与雷夫经手的海洛因有关
traced back to the heroin Rev's moving.
你们还想等到别的孩子因此丧命吗
You want to wait for another kid to die?
我们采取上门谈话策略  行吗
We'll do a knock-and-talk, all right?
出来应门的那个人行为古怪
Whoever's in control of the apartment gets all squirrelly,
我们从那里入手
we'll take it from there.
行吗
All right?
我们准备上去了
We're going back up.
你们原地待命
Stand by.
已经潜入  随时待命  长官
Tucked in and ready to go, boss.
用烤肉酱腌肉
Barbecue sauce as a marinade?
那是你们波多黎各的吃法
What's that--some kind of Puerto Rican thing
-还是什么  -我是多米尼加人
- or something? - I'm Dominican.
那里面的糖太多了  会毁了肉味
It's got too much sugar in it. It'll burn the meat.
呼叫指挥中心  有人持枪袭警
10-1! Shots fired at the police!
呼叫指挥中心  翡翠区5600号
10-1, 5600 Emerald!
有便衣警察在现场
Plainclothes officers at the scene!
去拿长枪
Get the long guns!
快回屋里去  回楼上去
Get back inside! Go back upstairs!
收到
All right, man.
警察  这里安全
Police! Clear!
安全
Clear!
发现尸体
Body!
厕所里的死尸是雷夫
That's Rev in the john.
罪犯一定是惯犯
Offender must have booked.
让支援进来  搜查整幢楼
Call it in. Clear the rest of the building.
开枪的人仍在附近
Shooter's in the wind.
芝加哥
警署
第一季
第一集
带他上楼
Take him upstairs.
斩首
Beheading--
那是贩毒集团独有的手段
that's a signature Cartel move.
是的
Yeah.
琳德赛  回想一下开门人的外貌特征
Lindsay, put together a description of the guy who answered the door,
查查我们的数据库里有没有他的资料
see if you can find him in any of our databases.
你的无线电发射器还好吗
Hey, is your transmitter all right?
-信号切断了  -对了
- It cut out. - Oh, yeah.
不小心撞到墙了
Uh, banged up against the wall.
抱歉  吉恩
I'm sorry, Jin.
埃尔文  找个新人
Alvin, I'm gonna need a fresh face
以防再需要人假扮买家
in case we have someone pose as a buyer again.
我从警校里找个人来
I'll pull someone from the academy.
谢了
I owe you one.
这就是同事的作用
That's why you have backup.
普拉特  开枪的人有消息吗
Hey, Platt, anything on the shooter?
还在仔细搜寻
Still doing a grid search,
派了直升机  目前没有线索
brought in the helicopter-- nothing yet.
暴力犯罪部门的拜尔登警督找你
Lieutenant Belden from violent crimes is looking for you.
伯吉斯  伯吉斯
Hey, Burgess. Burgess?
-在  -过来
- Yeah. - Come here.
有活儿给你
I got a job for you.
去趟停尸房
Hit the morgue.
罗斯·赫菲尔德  昨天送去的尸体
D.O.A. was brought in today named Ross Herrfeldt.
是我表弟
He's my cousin.
我很遗憾
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
谢谢
Thanks.
他左手戴着一只钻石尾戒
He's got a diamond pinkie ring on his left hand.
你去帮我拿来
I want you to get it for me.
找一个叫戴夫·博海克的人就行
Ask for a guy named Dave Bulhack down there.
说是我派你去的就行了
Tell him I sent ya. It'll be fine.
-可是  -应该没问题
- I don't-- - It shouldn't be a problem.
那戒指很有纪念意义
It's got a lot of sentimental value.
得赶在那群黄鼠狼亲戚来之前拿到
I need to get it before the hyena in-laws move in.
去吧  拿着这个  去吧
So go. Take the thing and go.
快去
Go, go, go.
-那孩子多大了  -十三岁
- And how old is the kid? - 13.
没有父母陪同  不能进行询问
You can't interview him without parental consent.
他爸死了  他妈在监狱
Dad's dead. Mom's in jail.
我请示过儿童家庭服务管理局
I notified D.C.F.S.
他们怎么说
And they said what?
我给他们留言了
I left a message.
醉醺醺地跟一群家伙鬼混是一回事
You know, running around half-cocked in a gang unit is one thing,
掌管整个情报部却完全是另一回事
but being the boss of an intelligence unit is another matter entirely.
我的队伍由我来管  警督
I run my squad as I see fit, Lieutenant.
你的侦探工作我不管
You do your detective work how you want.
警长  这是联合调查
This is a joint investigation, sergeant.
所有信息都要共享
We share all information.
我正要去找你
I was gonna come to you.
我们离得也不远
Nah, we're a block and a half away.
再说  轮到我遛狗了
My turn to walk the mutt, besides.
对了  我想找你谈一笔合作
So, look, I got a business proposition for you.
-是吗  -对
- Yeah, huh? - Yeah.
我经常办一些内容丰富的派对
I throw these full-package-type parties--
有DJ  有游戏  一应俱全
DJ, games, the whole deal.
客源挺稳定的  他们一直跟着我
Got a pretty steady crowd. They follow me.
唯一的问题是  我办派对的地方破产了
Only problem is, my venue fell through,
所以我在想  不如改到莫利酒吧
and I'm thinking, how about Molly's?
-被砍头了吗  -是啊  太无语
- Beheaded? - Yeah, you believe that?
酒吧内的消费收益都归你
So you can have the whole bar,
酒吧进门费我们平分
and me and you can split the door.
等等  谁被砍头了
Whoa, wait. Who got beheaded?
一个毒贩子
Oh, some dealer.
所有宣传我来做
I'll take care of all the promotions,
而且我还会派人负责安保
and I'll provide security at the front.
听起来好复杂  不过没问题
Uh, it sounds complicated, but, yeah.
给我二百美元  你叫谁来都行
Just give me a flat $200, and you can invite who you want.
-成交  -好的
- Done. - All right.
走了  旺发  快点
Come on, Pouch! Come on!
我听说雷夫在找跑腿的人
I heard Rev was looking for a runner--
帮他买饭  买烟
You know, get his lunch and smokes
买彩票什么的
and lottery tickets and stuff.
所以我就去看能不能拿到这份工作
So I went over there to see if I could get the job.
有人敲了门
Someone knocked on the door.
他就出去了  我听到有人喊叫
He went out of the room. I heard yelling.
所以我就躲进了衣柜里
And that's when I ducked into that closet.
我们的记录里面有你的名字  德安东尼
You're in our gang database, D'Anthony.
我们知道你跟雷夫是一伙的
We know you were in the same crew as Rev.
他惹到什么人了吗
Did he piss someone off?
有没有人想找他报仇
Was someone moving in on his action?
你看到雷夫身上发生的事了吗
You see what happened to Rev?
没
No.
我听到了
I heard it.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
你听到什么了
What all did you hear?
有三个人
There were three of them.
你看到他们的长相了吗
Did you get a good look at them?
没有  一听到喊声我就藏起来了
No, I hid as soon as I heard yelling.
他们说什么了
What were they saying?
不知道  大部分是西班牙语
I don't know. Most of it was in Spanish.
有听到名字吗
How about a name?
我不知道那是不是名字
I don't know if it was a name,
不过雷夫一直在喊"八爪"
but Rev kept yelling out "Pulpo."
不会是同一个"八爪"吧
Can't be the same Pulpo.
就是他
That's him.
亚德勒斯·迪亚斯
Adres Dias,
外号"八爪"
aka Pulpo,
也就是章鱼
the octopus.
哥伦比亚和美国双重国籍
He's got dual citizenship here and Colombia.
五年前我跟茱尔斯接触过他
Me and Jules had him on our radar five years back
当时他还是个正在往上爬的街头暴徒
when he was working his way up from street enforcer.
是啊  我记得他的名字
Yeah, I remember his name.
他当时是不是杀了两个人
Didn't he beat a double-murder rap?
两名关键证人都被杀了
The two key witnesses were killed.
他当时也喜欢砍别人的头吗
Was he cutting off heads back then too?
不  他在哥伦比亚学了点东西
No, he learned a thing or two since he was in Colombia.
-是吗  -他是哪种人
- Oh. - What type of player was he?
城里哪些地盘是他的
What part of the city did he hold down?
这就是问题所在
Oh, see, that's the thing.
他不属于任何帮派
He wasn't affiliated with any faction.
没人知道他的真正情况
Nobody knew his real script.
他就是因为金钱和暴力干这行的
He was just in it for the money and the blood.
好了  你们两个来我办公室
Okay, you two, in my office.
你有没有听说过一句老话
You ever heard the expression
"百分之十的警察干了百分之九十的活"
"10% percent of the cops do 90% of the work"?
听过
I have.
我们情报组就属于那百分之十
Well, this intelligence unit is part of the 10%.
所以  我很欣赏你的进取心
With that said, I appreciate your aggressiveness,
但是给你的命令是去卧底买毒品
but you were instructed to do an undercover buy
不能进门
in the doorway.
我从没让你跨过门槛
I never told you to cross the threshold.
如果当时你进去了
If you had,
你和琳德赛可能就不会活着走出来了
you and Lindsay might not have gotten out of there alive.
你推荐进来的人  你看好他
You vouched for him. Keep him in line.
咱们出去转一圈
Let's go for a ride.
-你推荐谁  -吉普森
- Who do you have? - Gibson--
我们手头最好的学员...
hands down the best cadet we got--
超级敬业
super dedicated,
从不顶嘴  从不掉链子
no back talk, no ball breaking,
枪法高超
aced the marksmanship.
你要等他毕业后再用他吗
You need him when he's finished with the academy?
我马上就需要他
I needed him five minutes ago.
-好的  -你想自杀
- All right. - You want to kill yourself?
有本事让我来
You know what? I'll do it.
我打爆你脑子如何
I'll blow your brains out, huh?
你觉得怎么样
Huh? What do you think about that?
你搞什么
What the hell are you doing?
你说目标是让他放下手里的枪
You said the goal was to get the gun out of his hands.
就要他了
We'll take him.
我可以找几个我的线人
Hey, I got a couple of C.I.s I can reach out to,
看他们知不知道"八爪"的消息
see if they know anything about Pulpo.
很好
Good.
我们现在是要去见你的线人吗
Is that who we're going to see, a C.I. of yours?
差不多
Basically.
这是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
到底是还是不是
Either they are or they aren't.
我给你有重要安排
I got big plans for you.
留在这
Stay here.
这就是你的重要安排  让我留在车里
That's your big plan -- for me to stay in the car?
那你带我来干什么
What'd you bring me for, then?
你能带给我好心情
You cheer me up.
最近怎么样  莫里斯
What's up, Maurice?
让我猜猜
Let me guess...
雷夫
Rev.
妄想当老大的人
Wannabe shot callers, man.
那些蠢货还没学会走路
These fools want to grind it up to sixth gear
就想先学会跑
before they even know how to drive.
他和哪个贩毒团伙在合作
He got in bed with a cartel?
哥伦比亚的
Colombians.
"八爪"这个名字有印象吗
The name Pulpo mean anything to you?
没有
No.
雷夫的手下有谁可能了解情况
Who in Rev's posse might know something?
有个替他分销毒品的
He subcontracted the transport --
一个叫库珀的白佬
some white dude named Coop.
这是姓还是名
That a first or last name?
自己去查
Look it up.
我不能把你的活全干了吧
What, I got to do everything for you?
过几周我会需要你
I'm gonna need you in a couple weeks.
帮我解决些"交通"问题
Direct some traffic for me.
你要做的是等我的消息
You'll wait to hear from me is what you'll do.
你得搞清楚状况
What's the matter with you?
埃里克·库珀
Eric Cooper!
库珀  开门
Hey, Coop, open up!
有撬痕
Pry marks.
冲进去
Breach.
警察
Police!
安全
Clear!
警察
Police!
安全
Clear!
我下次看到的头最好是"八爪"的
The next head I see better be Pulpo's.
戴夫·博海克在吗
Hi. Um, is Dave Bulhack here?
他生病回家了
He went home sick.
好吧
Oh, okay.
21区的普拉特警长派我来的
Um, Sergeant Platt from the 21st sent me.
那个老巫婆  她想要什么
Oh, that witch? What does she need?
刚送到的一名死者  叫罗斯·赫菲尔德
Well, a D.O.A. was brought in named Ross Herrfeldt,
我们在他身上找不到合法的身份证明
and we didn't get the proper identifiers on him.
我需要照几张照片拿到数据库对比
I need to take some photos, so we can cross-match.
好的  这...不好意思
OK -- um, this is embarrassing,
你有没有呕吐袋之类的
but do you have a barf bag or something?
我有点难受
I got hit with a wave here.
抱歉
Sorry.
在这等着
Just wait here.
过来
Hey, come here.
亚当·鲁塞克  这位是博伊特警长
Adam Ruzek, this is Sergeant Voight.
很高兴认识你  长官
Hey, boss. Nice to meet you, sir.
鲁塞克  我听过这个名字
Ruzek -- I know that name.
是的  我父亲鲍勃曾是巡警
Yeah, my dad, Bob, was a patrolman.
-在26区干了一辈子  -我记得
- His whole career in the 26th. - You don't say.
是我把他带出警校的  不是因为他父亲
I pulled him out of the academy, not his old man.
你和我父亲一起工作过吗
What, did you work with my dad?
是的  我们之前在同一支
Yeah, we were on the same...
-棒球队  -在同一支棒球队
- Softball. - Softball team together.
我们一起设计T恤  如果我没记错的话
We designed T-shirts, if I'm not mistaken.
是啊  孩子  比弗利的生活很不错的
Yeah, boy, there's some good living up in Beverly.
你是在那长大的  对吗
That's where you were raised, right?
我和我父亲在那度过了不少时间
I split time with my dad there.
还和我母亲在卡纳里维尔住过
and my mom up in Canaryville.
如果德安东尼说的是真的
If D'Anthony was right,
他听见公寓里有三个人的说话声
and he heard three voices in the apartment,
"八爪"一定是从麦德林带了两个打手来
Pulpo must have brought two hit men with him from Medellin.
很好  把这些情报都告诉
All right, just get all this information
暴力犯罪科的拜尔登警督
to lieutenant Belden in Violent Crimes.
对了  他给过我们什么情报吗
Hey, have we gotten anything from his end?
没有
Nothing.
雷夫和库珀昨天的通话记录显示
Calls between Rev and Coop yesterday--
只有一个号码都打给过他们两个人
only one other number called 'em both.
是预充值的一次性手机  已经没信号了
It's a pay-as-you-go drop phone, signal's off,
不过是在希腊城的一家手机店买的
but it was purchased at a cell store in Greektown.
你跟霍尔斯特德一起去查查
Take Halstead. Check it out.
小子  我要你像个卡纳里维尔人
Hey, I want the Canaryville out of you,
别来公子哥做派  知道吗
not the Beverly, huh?
明白  老大  没问题
You got it, boss. Yeah.
-你好  -你好  我叫亚当·鲁塞克
- Hey. - Hey, man. Adam Ruzek.
-安东尼奥  -茱尔斯  欢迎
- Antonio. - Jules. Welcome.
我们俩搭档多久了  一个月吗
How long have we worked together--a month?
我觉得是该坦诚相见的时候了
I think it's time we could be honest with each other.
你同意吗
Wouldn't you agree?
-不同意  -两条意见
- No. - Two things--
第一  一直都是你开车  我可不干
One, you driving all the time, I'm not down with that.
前辈优先
Seniority rules.
我当警察的时间更长
I've been on the job longer.
我在这个队里的时间更长
I've been in this unit longer.
好吧  我觉得自己像个家庭主夫
Okay, look, I feel like a househusband.
第二条是什么
What's the second thing?
你和博伊特是怎么回事
What's the deal with you and Voight?
不要告诉别人
This stays between us.
当然
Of course.
我们一起去的毕业舞会
We went to prom together.
我说  他是不是你的秘密老爸什么的
I mean, is he your secret dad or something?
我换个问法  如果我想约你出去
Put it this way-- if I were to ask you out,
是不是要先征得他同意
would I have to get his permission first?
如果哪个男人约我之前还想我爸同意
Any guy who needs to ask my dad's permission to date me
他还是省省吧
should save himself the trouble.
条儿够正啊  小妞
Uh! Shake it, baby.
嘴巴干净点
Watch yourself.
遵命  警官大人
Yes, sir, officer, sir.
过去24小时里有人在你店里
A pay-as-you-go phone was purchased
买走了一部预充值手机
from your store in the last 24 hours.
我们想找找是谁买的
We're looking for who bought it.
是的
Yeah.
昨天一个叫胡安·加西亚的人  付的现金
A Juan Garcia yesterday, paid cash.
你还能提供什么别的线索吗
Any other information you can provide us?
没有  我们可不负责背景调查
No. We're not responsible for background checks.
的确  不过这名字太常见了
True, but it is a fairly common name.
-我们也没什么办法  -是的
- You know, there's not a lot we can do with that. - Yeah.
你们别教我怎么做生意
You don't tell me how to do my job.
我也不管你们怎么当警察
I don't tell you how to do yours.
你是格伦·皮尔森  对吗  这里的店主
You're Glen Pearson, right-- the owner of this place?
是的
That's right.
好像有个叫格伦·皮尔森的家伙
You know, it looks like there's a Glen Pearson
在印第安纳州的加里
with a deceptive practice and fraud charge
因为卖赃被指控欺诈
for selling stolen merchandise out of Gary, Indiana.
是吗
Oh?
这是一张两万五千元的可引渡扣押逮捕令
That's a $25,000 extraditable must-hold warrant.
-真狠  -你觉得...
- Oy. - What do you think--
身高  体重  眼睛颜色是不是都符合
height,  weight match, eye color too?
对  不过我不敢说  我不喜欢草率下结论
Yeah, but I don't know. I hate to jump to conclusions.
你知道吗  我有办法了
You know what? I got an idea.
不如我们先把他铐上
Why don't we throw some bracelets on him?
带回局里  比对下指纹
We'll take him down to the station, run his prints,
-然后就知道了  -我这里有个监控探头
- and then we can be sure. - I got a nanny cam up here.
我可以调出监控录像
I can pull some footage,
找到买手机那人的照片
get a picture of the guy who did it--
我能做的只有这么多了
that's the best I can do.
-太好了  -很好
- Oh. That's great. - Great, yeah.
你真是个好人
You're too kind.
-就知道会管用  -是的
- Knew that would work. - Mm-hmm.
只要找到是哪个笨蛋买的手机就行了
Just got to figure out who this idiot is.
没事的时候撅着小翘臀去我家玩玩吧  小妞
Why don't you bring that ass over to my place sometime, girl?
我给你"开门"
I'll let you in.
算了吧
Oh, let it go.
-好的  -随你
- Uh-huh. - Uh-huh.
过来  小子
Hey, come here a sec.
不  你想诈我动手
No, you're just trying to get me
好算我袭警把我抓起来
with assaulting a police officer.
你看到我戴警徽了吗
Do you see a badge on me?
还有谁想来
Anybody else?
大英雄啊
My hero.
你还是别想开车
You're still not driving.
再说一次  节哀顺变  警长
Again, I'm sorry for your loss, Sergeant.
他就是个老赖
Yeah, he was a deadbeat.
他两年前装地上游泳池的时候
I loaned him 500 bucks for an above-ground pool
跟我借了五百块
he put in two years ago.
你猜他还给我多少
Guess how much I got back.
-不知道  -猜猜看
- I don't know. - Guess.
-一分没还吗  -对
- Nothing? - That's right.
在西瑟马克有间胡里奥当铺
So Julio's Pawnshop on west Cermak--
你现在过去该关门了
Ugh. It'll be closed by the time you get there.
所以明天过去  找胡里奥本人
So tomorrow ask for Julio.
别和她老婆做生意  她会坑你的
Do not deal with his wife, 'cause she'll dick you down.
我要这戒指最少当到三百五
I want $350 for this thing, minimum.
好的  胡里奥当铺
Okay, yeah, yeah, Julio's.
知道了
Got it.
哥伦比亚当局证明此人叫奥马尔·罗哈斯
Colombian authorities I.D.'d this guy as Omar Rojas,
-自由职业杀手  -那么雷夫是老大
- freelance hit man. - So Rev was the boss.
库珀负责运货
Coop moved the merchandise.
他们这指挥系统的下一个人是谁
Who's the next in the chain of command?
问题就在这里
Well, that was the problem.
雷夫刚从巴吞鲁日回来一年
Rev was only in town from Baton Rouge for a year.
他的势力还没成型
There was no structure to his crew.
-没人有进展吗  -没有
- And nobody's talking? - Nope.
好吧  等奥林斯基来了  你告诉他...
All right. When Olinsky gets in, you tell him...
我在这呢
I'm right here.
移民管理局有什么发现吗
Anything from your C.I.S?
没什么发现  就想着
No dice, something about not wanting
怎么不掉脑袋
to have their heads chopped off.
好吧  把罗哈斯和八爪的照片发到全市
All right, get Rojas' image out there with Pulpo's citywide,
所有的机场  火车站  汽车站
all airports, train, bus stations,
然后继续追查
and keep hitting the bushes.
有什么新进展要告诉我吗
You want to brief me on any new developments?
我也正想问你
I was about to ask you the same thing.
如果我们有什么进展  你会第一个知道
If we came up with something, you'd be the first to know.
我不是在跟你抢功
This ain't about who takes credit.
案子结了的话  最后还有由你去风光
End of the day, you can stand in front of the cameras.
但这个案子我们应该一起调查
But this is supposed to be a joint investigation,
这是你说的
your words.
可你那边什么消息都没有
We haven't heard dick from you
你手底下的警探也没人在查这个案子
or any of your detectives working this case.
好吧  这个我回头再问问
Okay, I'll double-check on that.
那个13岁的孩子怎么样了
Now, what's with the 13-year-old kid?
还在这里
Still here.
-他说什么了吗  -说得够多了
- He give you anything? - Enough.
那就把他送走
Okay, then kick him.
不  他的事已经解决了  警督
No, that's been handled, lieutenant.
佩里指挥官在罪犯被监护前
Commander Perry has given me another day
又给了我一天时间
till we get the offenders into custody.
这是为了那个孩子的安全着想
It's for the kid's own safety.
法律就是法律  博伊特
The law's the law, Voight.
你向指挥官求情时
I'm sure you left that part out
肯定把这忘得一干二净
when you were doing a soft shoe for your commander.
我告诉你
I'm telling you,
根据我和副总警监哈蒙德的谈话
based on my conversation with Deputy Chief Hammond,
如果你不打算起诉这孩子
if you're not gonna charge this kid,
那就通知他的家人
then notify his relatives
叫他们来把人接走
and have 'em come and pick him up.
再说一次  还用我来这
And the fact that I'm here, once again,
向你解释最基本的警察规定
explaining to you basic police protocol
就是为什么大家不愿意
is a prime example why people are reluctant
让你插手热门案件的最好说明
to bring you into the loop during these type of heater cases.
你表兄伦尼会来接你
Your cousin Renny's coming to pick you up.
现在吗
Now?
第21区
收到
Copy that.
跟我来
Come here.
跟你说  我主要就是靠观察人生活的
You know, I basically look people in the eye for a living.
走出这个圈子你也有自己的未来  德安东尼
You have a future beyond this neighborhood, D'Anthony.
谁都有自己的未来
It's OK to want that.
你想走出去的话
When you start to try and get out,
不论何时
whenever that is,
尽管找我
you call me.
■
亨利·博伊特
芝加哥警署警长
该走了
Let's go!
你好  老兄
Hey. What's up, man?
-你好  -嘿
- What's going on? - Hey.
我们进来都不打折
We had to pay full cover at the door.
我这是做生意  警探
I'm running a business, detective.
阿特沃特特别抠门儿
Atwater is the cheapest,
绝对是你们见过最抠门儿的
I mean the cheapest guy you will ever meet.
我们昨天开车...让我说完
We drove...wait for it,
我们开车找了半小时自动取款机
we drove around for a half hour yesterday looking for an ATM
就为了找个不收手续费的
that wouldn't charge him a withdrawal fee.
最低消费要喝两杯哦
And there's a two-drink minimum,
快点喝吧  我可不是逗你们哦
so start knocking 'em back. I ain't playing.
好吧  那我也想用你那种杯子
Okay, then I want mine in that cup.
-下次吧  -你做过飞机乘务员
- Next time. - Flight attendant.
是的  干了三年
Uh, yeah, three years,
直到我进警校
waiting until I got into the police academy.
乘务员吗
Flight attendant?
你们想怎么取笑我随便
You can break my balls all you want,
但做乘务员让我更好地学会了控制人群
but I learned more about crowd control
解决冲突还有恐吓战术
and conflict resolution and intimidation tactics,
如果你们选我进情报机构的话
traits that will serve me well when you guys detail me
这些会对我有很大帮助  明白了吧
up into intelligence. Hint, hint.
-好吧  记住了  -谢谢  说说你吧
- Okay. Noted. - Thanks. How about you?
我就普普通通  没什么光辉事迹
Oh, I just kicked around, nothing glamorous.
-你呢  -我当过兵
- You? - I was in the military.
-你亲眼见过战斗吗  -见过
- You see any action? - I did. Yeah.
跟现在你的工作有相似之处吗
Ever see anything like you did today?
抱歉  我...
I'm sorry. I...
就当我没问  问题太蠢了
Forget I asked that. That was a stupid question.
好吧
All right.
合作愉快
Let's do this again.
就先这样
All right.
两百块
200 bucks?
你知道吗  如果你在门口收钱的话
You realize if you split the money at the door,
我们可以赚到这个数的五倍
we would have made five times as much?
我知道
Yep.
喂
Hello?
你在哪里
Where are you?
怎么回事
What happened?
因为我躲在衣柜里他们很生气
They got pissed at me for hiding in the closet.
他们说我应该跟雷夫一伙儿
Said I should have backed Rev up.
我想离开这里
I want to get out.
过来
Come on.
-你现在白班夜班都干活啊  -老爸
- You working double-time now? - Hey, dad.
-宝贝  -亲爱的
- Hey, baby. - Hey, baby.
他喜欢这里
Oh, he loves it here.
-那在这里待的时间也有点久了  -没事的
- A little too much maybe. - It's fine.
我要带他去打拳击的  对吧
I got to get him into boxing, right?
等他十岁了再说  我们说好了的
When he's ten. We talked about this.
-伊娃呢  -打排球去了
- Where's Eva? - Volleyball.
然后她要在朋友家借宿一晚
Then she's got a sleepover at a friend's.
好吧  我得回去工作了
All right. Got to get back to work.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait.
-那晚餐怎么办  -我们突然有任务要做
- What about dinner tonight? - Something jumped off.
-你还记得八爪吗  -那是鲨鱼的意思吧
- Do you remember Pulpo? - Yeah, that means shark, right?
是章鱼
Octopus.
姑娘  你得好好练习西班牙语了
Girl, you got to work on your Spanish.
好吧  一有空我就会练习的
Okay, sure, in all that free time I have.
他又回来了
Yeah, well, he's back in town.
过来  儿子
Hey, come here.
-你是最棒的  -你更棒
- You're the best. - You're better.
所以怎么办  你搞定把我弄出来的事吗
So how would this work-- you getting me out and all?
你不用管
Leave that to me.
可能得花上几天
And it may take a couple days.
你只要能活到那时就行
I just need you to stay alive till then.
你这么做有什么好处
What's in it for you?
你是个好孩子
You're a good kid.
我不用做什么吗  比如内应之类的
I don't got to work it off-- like be a snitch or something?
我不会去做的
'Cause that ain't happening.
不用
No.
但如果我想告诉你一些事
But if I wanted to tell you something,
不是因为你给我钱
not because you were paying me,
而是因为我想要告诉你的话
but because I wanted to tell you,
那我就不算是内应了
that don't make me no snitch.
我们就是吃了顿饭  聊了聊天而已
Just two guys breaking bread, having a conversation.
我没看见有"饭"
I don't see no bread.
这是个俗语
It's an expression.
好吧  我听到一些大人说话了
Okay, well, I heard some of the older guys talking.
他们还会再干掉一个
There's gonna be one more hit.
谁
Who?
我不知道
I don't know...
但是泽维尔知道  泽维尔·格林
But Xavier would-- Xavier Green.
是他处理的雷夫的事
He dealt for Rev.
钱呢
Where's the money?
我接到了验尸员打来的电话
I got a call from the M.E.'s office.
-他们在找这个  -他们怎么会找上你
- They're looking for this. - How'd they get a hold of you?
肯定是因为我登记离开了
From when I signed out, apparently.
你登记了  你登记干什么
You signed--you weren't supposed to sign out.
你没跟我说不能登记啊  警长
Well, that's something that you neglected to tell me, Sergeant.
别把这事扯到我身上
Do not bring me into this!
警长  你为什么要为难我呢
Sergeant, why are you breaking my balls here?
因为你这个人软弱没胆
'Cause you don't have any.
露丝·德怀尔  验尸官
Ruth Dwyer, M.E.'s office.
她在等你给她回电话
She's expecting your call.
在我们到之前  你就得
The drugs got to be in your mitts
把毒品拿到手  否则我们就会一无所获
before we can move in-- otherwise, we got nothing.
-好的  -好吗
- Yeah. - All right?
如果他要指责你什么的话
Now, if he starts accusing you of anything,
你就愤怒火大地还击
you throw it right back in his face, pissed off and indignant.
要愤怒  火大
Pissed off and indignant.
这是你最好的两个小伙伴
Those are your two best friends.
-我能做到  -现在  我朋友吉恩
- That I can do. - Now, my friend Jin here
给你配置最新的无线电传输设备
is gonna hook you up with the latest in radio transmission.
我们早就不用把线拴你命根子上那一套了
Department's come a long way since taping a wire to your taint.
这是什么
What is that?
随身听没有了吗
You run out of walkmans?
新来的家伙破坏力太强了
New guys keep breaking 'em.
这里
Here.
拿着这把小钥匙
Just take your little key,
打开你那神秘的小抽屉
go to your little special drawer,
给我拿点高端洋气的东西来  去吧
and get me something top shelf, come on.
好吧
All right.
别上那辆车  别进那栋楼
Don't get in the car, don't go in the building,
别去任何我们看不到的地方
don't go anywhere we don't have any eyeball on ya.
明白吗
You understand that?
明白
Understand that.
记住  奇多
All right, and remember... Cheeto.
-奇多  -奇多
- Cheeto. - Cheeto.
奇多  好吧  我记住了
Cheeto. All right. I got it.
这可是保你命的
It's your lifeline.
用完记得拿回来
I want this back.
-好了  -我们上吧
- All right? - Let's do it.
有事吗  伙计
Hey, what's up, gents?
你有什么需要吗
Need something?
你怎么知道我在卖东西
How you know I'm selling?
大胆猜的
A wild guess.
我原来是从几个街区外的奇多那儿买
I used to buy from Cheeto a couple blocks up,
但我猜他大概度假去了吧
but I guess he went on vacation.
是啊  长假呢  你有多少钱
Yeah, a long one. How much you got?
-现在有300大洋  -不错呀
- $300 just for now. - Cool.
-很好  -是啊
- Cool, cool. - Yeah.
给我300  然后20分钟后回来
You give me that $300 and come back in, like, 20 minutes.
好的  毒贩子先生
Oh, okay, Mr. Drug dealer,
我把钱都给你了
I'll just give you all my money.
还能出什么乱子不成
What could possibly go wrong?
把钱给我  然后从我的地盘滚开
Give me the cash, and then get your skinny ass off my block.
兄弟  我一周能在伊立诺州立大学卖一盎司
Dude, I sell an ounce a week up at UIC.
你是想在这儿跟我大吵大闹
You want to sit here and play barney badass with me
然后坑我300大洋
and break me off for 300 bucks,
还是想一周挣2000
or would you like to make $2,000 a week?
你说呢
Huh?
300美元我给你4克
I'll give you 4 grams for $300.
不不不  5克
No, no, no, no, no. You'll give me 5.
最好别在里面混别的东西  否则就没回头客了
It better not be stepped on, or I'm not gonna be back.
你们相信他吗
You believe this guy?
听着  兄弟  给我个准信
Listen, bro, I need an answer,
34分钟后我还有一场社会学的期中考试
'cause I got a sociology midterm in 34 minutes.
我可不是在开玩笑  快点
I'm not even joking. Huh? Come on.
-你不能迟到  -先生  当然不能
- You can't be late for class. - No, sir, I cannot.
-警察  举起手来  -警察
- Police! Get your hands up! - Police!
-举起手来  -警察
- Put 'em up! - Police!
-举起手来  -等等  你们是警察吗
- Get 'em up! - Wait, you're cops?
-举起手  举起手来  -举起手来
- Hands up! Get 'em up! - Hands up!
-举起手来  -快给我举起手来
- Put 'em up! - Hands up now!
这是我听过最棒的提议了  对吗
I mean, this is the sweetest offer I've ever heard, right?
你告诉我们那群哥伦比亚人的下一个目标
You tell us who the Colombians are targeting next,
我们就不会以贩毒的罪名起诉你
and we won't charge you with distribution.
-还想讨价还价吗  -我可不做交易
- What's the debate? - Ain't no debate.
警察嘴里说出来的话  我一句都不信
I just know not to trust a word that comes out of a cop's mouth.
我们是想救人性命
We're trying to save someone's life.
你们在担心我的人吗
You all worried about my boy?
不劳费心  他都准备好了
Don't. He's ready.
哥伦比亚人要是想对他下手
The Colombians try to make a move on him,
他们肯定有去无回
it'll be the last move they try and make.
他们也准备好了
They were ready too.
我们要找一位名叫谢恩·卡梅伦的男子
We're looking for a Shane Cameron.
泽维尔说他昨天就躲起来了
Xavier says he's been in hiding since yesterday.
没错  但他在艾迪生开了一家廉价旅馆
Yeah, but he has a flophouse over on Addison.
也许值得查一查
Might be worth checking out.
好的  大伙儿都去换好装备
All right, everybody vest up.
今天博伊特是怎么回事
What's up Voight's ass today?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
你该知道吧
You would.
那张名片...
The card--
芝加哥警署
亨利·博伊特警探
团伙犯罪专家
团伙犯罪调查部
你保存多久了
How old is that thing?
13年了
13 years.
想跟我聊聊吗
Want to tell me about it?
他救了我一命  所以我来了这里
The man saved my life, and here I am.
你还想知道更多吗
Oh, you want to know more about that?
那你得请我喝几杯了
It's gonna cost you a couple of drinks.
远离孩子  还有精彩的故事可听
Hey, a night away from the kids and a juicy story--
这样的夜晚  我很乐意买单
happy to buy.
-2楼B座吗  -没错
- 2B? - Yeah.
没问题的  警督  我们能搞定
It's okay, lieutenant. We got it covered.
如果他在楼上  我会通知您的
I'll let you know if he's upstairs.
谁
Who?
谢恩·卡梅伦  我给您留言了
Shane Cameron. I left you a message.
我们在追踪一辆车
We're following up on the car.
什么车
What car?
比对昨天离开库珀谋杀案现场车辆牌照后
Plate match to a black four-door
我们发现是一辆黑色四门车
seen leaving the scene of the Coop murder yesterday.
应该停在这附近
Supposed to be parked around here.
没人告诉我这个信息啊
I never got that info.
好吧  那肯定是我疏忽了
Yeah, I must have dropped the ball on that.
终止行动  撤退
Terminate. Pull back.
目标也许就在这栋建筑里
Targets may be in the building.
茱尔斯
Jules.
需要紧急援助  警员中枪了
10-1! Officer shot!
-出去  快出去  -快点
- Outside! Outside!  - Come on!
你不会有事的
You're gonna be all right.
-茱尔斯  -挺住啊
- Jules? - Hang in there.
就在那边
Over there.
那是谁  快追
Who is that? Go!
是八爪
It's Pulpo!
你会没事的  茱尔斯
You're gonna be okay, Jules.
我们得马上出发  把她抬进救护车
We got to move! Get her in the ambo.
她会没事的  对吗
She's gonna be okay, right?
我们得立刻送她去医院
We got to go right now.
中枪部位在锁骨中线
Mid-clavicular.
我跟你一起去  护士
I'm coming with you, sister.
立即静脉注射
Start an I.V.
茱尔斯  看着我
Jules, look at me.
没事的  你会没事的
You're okay. It's gonna be okay.
追  快追
Go! Go!
-追  拦住那家伙  -我知道
- Go, stop the guy. - I got it.
安全
Clear!
站住
Stop!
你死定了  先生
Estas muerto, senor.
闭嘴
Shut up!
-你死定了  -闭上你的臭嘴
- Estas muerto. - Shut your mouth!
-你死定了  -抓获一名罪犯
- Estas muerto. - One offender in custody.
什么事
Yeah.
茱尔斯没挺过去
Jules didn't make it.
是你  是你在背后搞的鬼
You. You played games.
退后  博伊特
Back up, Voight.
是你玩的把戏把她害死了
You played games, and you got her killed!
-有本事  现在就冲我来啊  -退后
- Hey, come on, now! - Back up!
来啊  你想玩是吧  放开我
Come on! You want to play? Get off of me!
-冷静点  -你想玩是吧
- Calm it down! - You want to play a game?
-有本事来啊  警长  -放开我
- Come on, Sarge! - Get off of me!
-博伊特  -有本事你来啊
- Voight! - Come on!
-送他出去  -放开我  放开我
- Get him out of here! - Get off of me! Get off of me!
安东尼奥
Antonio!
你还好吗
How are you?
-好久不见啊  -他们在哪
- It's been a while. - Where are they?
立刻告诉我那两个凶手的下落
I want your two hit men right now.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
看见了吗  这是我搭档的血
You see that? That's my partner's blood.
-安东尼奥  别这样  -快放开我
- Antonio! - Get off me! Get off!
安东尼奥
Antonio.
放开我
Get off!
坐下  给我坐下
Sit down. Sit down!
你得接这个电话
You need to take this.
什么事
Yeah?
安东尼奥...
Antonio...
安东尼奥  有人带走了迪戈
Antonio, s-someone's taken Diego.
他不见了
He's gone.